Izzy: Ben! Are you OK?
Ben: Yeah, I’m OK. I’m just really worried about Emma.
Izzy: Listen, your Aunt Jenny sent a message. She says your sister’s OK. She’s in hospital, but she’s OK.
Ben: She’s OK…She’s OK.
What a relief!
Izzy: Yeah. She’s OK.
Ben: Thanks…thanks for coming.
Izzy: Of course I came.
Ben: Oh, uh…How did the interview go?
Izzy: It went very well. I was amazing!
Ben: Of course you were. I knew it. When are they going to tell you if you got the job?
Izzy: They’re going to call me tomorrow.
Ben: I’m sure you’re going to get it!
Izzy: I hope so.
Announcement: The next train to Gatwick Airport leaves from platform thirteen.
Ben: That’s me.
See you, Izzy.
Izzy: When are you going to come back?
Ben: I don’t know.
In a week or two…It depends…
Izzy: See you when you get back.
Ben: Yeah. Uh,…here?
Izzy: Right here…well, if I’m not working in my cool new job.
Ben: Of course.
Izzy: Or if I’m just too busy to see you. Or if it’s raining!
Ben: I’m going to miss you, Izzy.
Bye.
Izzy: Bye.